http://www.mountainhighappliance.com/privacy-policy

Menu
ShopRefrigerationCookingLaundryDishwashersOutdoorVacuumsFood DisposalShop By BrandFrench Door RefrigeratorsSide by Side RefrigeratorsBuilt In RefrigeratorsBottom Freezer RefrigeratorsTop Mount RefrigeratorsSpecialty RefrigeratorsFreezersRefrigerator AccessoriesOvensRangesCooktopsMicrowavesHoodsAccessoriesSmall AppliancesWashersStack LaundryDryersLaundry AccessoriesDishwashersGrillsVacuumsTrash CompactorsDisposersShop All BrandsEventsBuildersDesignersClearanceStore LocationsRebates
X
Shop+Refrigeration+French Door RefrigeratorsSide by Side RefrigeratorsBuilt In RefrigeratorsBottom Freezer RefrigeratorsTop Mount RefrigeratorsSpecialty RefrigeratorsFreezersRefrigerator AccessoriesCooking+OvensRangesCooktopsMicrowavesHoodsAccessoriesSmall AppliancesLaundry+WashersStack LaundryDryersLaundry AccessoriesDishwashers+DishwashersOutdoor+GrillsVacuums+VacuumsFood Disposal+Trash CompactorsDisposersShop By Brand+Shop All BrandsEventsBuildersDesignersClearanceStore LocationsRebates
Website Privacy Statement
This document was last updated on May 13th, 2017.
ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
Mountain High Appliance is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing
https://www.mountainhighappliance.com, you acknowledge and fully understand
Mountain High Appliance’ Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.
PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in
Mountain High Appliance services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
Mountain High Appliance collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.
Web Server Logs.
When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:
Your Internet protocol address.
The kind of browser or computer you use.
Number of links you click within the site.
State or country from which you accessed the site.
Date and time of your visit.
Name of your Internet service provider.
Web page you linked to our site from.
Pages you viewed on the site.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.
Use of Cookies
Mountain High Appliance may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.
Mountain High Appliance reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into https://www.mountainhighappliance.com a site that relies on third-party cookies).
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.
Personal Information Users
Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.
We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:
To fulfill your service requests for services.
To protect ourselves from liability,
To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
BEHAVIORAL REMARKETING
Mountain High Appliance uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our website at https://www.mountainhighappliance.com . We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to https://www.mountainhighappliance.com.
Google
Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.
You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads
Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
Facebook
Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.
You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950
To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217
Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.
For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE
We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
SERVICE PROVIDERS
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.
However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.
USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES
https://www.mountainhighappliance.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow
Mountain High Appliance to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Mountain High Appliance may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.
Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Mountain High Appliance prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.
ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION
We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant --webmaster@ mountainhighappliance.com.
CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Mountain High Appliance has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
CONTACTING US
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at webmaster@
mountainhighappliance.com or send your comments to:
Mountain High Appliance Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel
601 E. 64th Ave., Building C, Suite 600Denver, Colorado 80229
Mountain High Appliance will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
Shop+
RefrigerationCookingLaundryDishwashersOutdoorVacuumsFood DisposalShop By Brand
Store Information+
About Us
Testimonials & Reviews
Financing
Extended Warranties
Delivery/Installation
More+
Events
EMAIL SIGNUP
Sign up for our newsletter and get exclusive offers from our favorite brands.
Subscribe
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Copyright © 2009 - 2020 Mountain High Appliance Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Welcome to our website! As we have the ability to list over one million items on our website (our selection changes all of the time), it is not feasible for a company our size to record and
playback the descriptions on every item on our website. However, if you are an American with a disability we are here to help you. Please call our disability services phone line at
719.596.3000 during regular business hours and one of our kind and friendly personal shoppers will help you navigate through our website, help conduct advanced searches, help you choose the item
you are looking for with the specifications you are seeking, read you the specifications of any item and consult with you about the products themselves.
There is no charge for the help of this personal shopper for any American with a disability. Finally, your personal shopper will explain our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service, and help you
place an order if you so desire.
